{
    "subject": "Olivia_Spencer",
    "predicate": "hasChild",
    "object": "Phillip_Spaulding",
    "human_readable": "Olivia Spencer has a child named Phillip Spalding.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8693925738334656,
            "question": "Who is Olivia Spencer's child?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8356103301048279,
            "question": "What is the name of Phillip Spalding's parent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8193658590316772,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Olivia Spencer and Phillip Spalding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.546629786491394,
            "question": "Does Olivia Spencer have any other children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5183435678482056,
            "question": "What is Phillip Spalding's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5037292838096619,
            "question": "How old is Phillip Spalding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4645553529262543,
            "question": "Does Phillip Spalding have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46449044346809387,
            "question": "What is Phillip Spalding's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3019380569458008,
            "question": "Where does Phillip Spalding live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1979031264781952,
            "question": "Is Olivia Spencer married?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Olivia Spencer has a child named Phillip Spalding.",
            "html": "yago_25012_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Phillip Spalding live?",
            "html": "yago_25012_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Phillip Spalding's profession?",
            "html": "yago_25012_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Phillip Spalding have any siblings?",
            "html": "yago_25012_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25012_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I found that the information does not support the triple.\n\nHere is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information supporting that Olivia Spencer has a child named Phillip Spaulding. According to the context, Olivia Spencer is married to Phillip Spaulding and had a daughter named Emma Spencer-Spaulding with him."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}